<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PocketYoga</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="abtyog">
        \t\t\tYoga is a well-known term these days, it is called a spiritual discipline that is based on a subtle science that aims at attaining harmony between body and mind. This is also referred to as science and art for achieving healthy living. The derivation of the word yoga is considered from the Sanskrit word Yuj. The meaning of Yuj is to join or yoke is to unite.
        
    \n\nYoga is safe and is practised even by kids and older people. There is no use of hard equipment, but only movements of the body for the extension. Yoga gives relaxation to not only the mind but also flexibility to the body.\n\n

        
<b><i>Origin of Yoga</i></b>
    \nIn India, the practice of yoga started centuries ago. In the present times as well,  it is followed by many due to its benefits for health as well as the overall life. Yoga has made several changes in the lifestyle of people. This is the inheritance embraced by centuries and will keep going for years. From working individuals to celebrities, everyone practices yoga to maintain a balanced life. Yoga helps to unite people in harmony and peace.
        
    \n\nCenturies ago, people belonging to Hinduism, Buddhism and Jainism started the following yoga and continued even now. Over the years, yoga experts have discovered different types of yoga offering numerous benefits. India is currently the centre stage of yoga and people from other countries visit India to practice it.
        
    \n\nCurrently, when the whole world is fighting against Coronavirus, yoga has gained its importance. The craze of yoga among people has increased so much and people are ready to join it via digital mode. Breathing practices have become a common practice for people as the medicines have not been introduced for the deadly virus.  Several mudras and postures are also recommended by the doctors during this time.\n\n

        
<b><i>Benefits of Yoga</i></b>
    \nAs mentioned above, yoga offers flexibility to the body and relaxation to the mind. There are different asanas practised by people, and each asana has its benefits on the mind and body. Yoga is designed to sharpen our minds and to improve our intelligence. Regular practice of yoga can help in controlling our emotions and promote well-being.
        
    \nSome Other Benefits of Practising Regular Yoga are -\n
    \t- It helps to develop self-discipline and self-awareness if practised regularly.\n
    \t- It helps to strengthen our flexibility and posture.\n
    \t- It increases muscle strength, tone and balances metabolism.\n
    \t- You will gain a sense of power as yoga helps to lead to a healthy life free of cost!\n
        
    \nBesides physical benefits, yoga also helps to benefit mentally in the long run. If you are stressed out, then practising yoga will bring change in your mental behaviour. If incorporated with meditation and breathing exercises, yoga will help to improve mental well-being.
        
    \n\nWe live in an age where we struggle to get mental peace. Professional and personal stress takes a toll on us. Lack of physical activities further builds stress. Practising yoga regularly can help in bringing calm, increasing body awareness, relief from chronic sleep patterns and others. Practising yoga can benefit you a long way. Many experts practice yoga and help by teaching the same.
        
    \n\nOn June 21, International Yoga Day is celebrated all across the world to make people aware of the benefits of yoga. It is the day to celebrate the gift the entire humankind has received and follow it full-fledgedly.\n\n

        
<b><i>Importance of Yoga</i></b>
    \nIt is essential to practice yoga daily to get benefits out of it. In this stressful lifestyle, practising workouts or yoga is very much important, and it can be greatly helpful, irrespective of age. It is the cheapest and free of cost treatment for all the health issues we face. From blood pressure to stress and body pain, everything gets under control on performing yoga regularly.
        
    \n\nThe main idea behind practising yoga is to control the body part movement using breathing exercises. There is no specific day to practice yoga. Depending on your schedule, you can practice this easy workout. However, it is highly recommended to practice yoga in the morning.\n\n

        
<b><i>Conclusion</i></b>
    \nYoga improves the quality of our life, and we need to work on it regularly. The main aim of writing this essay on yoga is to give you the primary picture of how yoga is beneficial for our life in the long run. You can practice or learn yoga from online classes or from expert. The ultimate aim is to make your life physically and mentally fit, which is a great challenge in this fast-paced life.
    </string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="about_yoga">About Yoga</string>
    <string name="yoga_mudras">Yoga Mudras</string>
    <string name="mantras">Mantras</string>
    <string name="bmi_calculator">bmi calculator</string>

</resources>

    